geniusnet.com 2017-11-24

# Privacy

Pursuant to Section 3 in the Terms of Genius Service, Please find the description for Genius’s Privacy Policy as below, which may be further stipulated or modified from time to time in this website without prior notice.

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you respond to a request for information. In order to make the best possible use of the service, you and/or company have to create agenius account.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used to improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and activities support needs)

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information. Although We will protect your personal information, however, there may be loopholes for information processing on the Internet. As a member, you agree to take the risks yourself inherent with online data transmission.When you use our websites, We will not be responsible for any service failures resulting from direct, indirect, additional, unexpected or deliberate damage. If some part of this service or any other related our Web experiences temporary disconnection, time delay, failure to transmit or restore data, or any loss resulted from infiltration by any third party, you agree not to claim any compensation from Our Web, and its related enterprises.

### Do we use cookies?

We do not use cookies. We actually use cookie. Do we need to mention that? 

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

### Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance!

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. Anyway, the Participants of this Activity must be at least 18 years old.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### Genius Web Service Tracking

KYE does not disclose any evaluations to any third party, the results are used for the sole purpose of improving our own webshop. 

### Your right to information, rectification, blocking or deletion of personal data

In compliance with the applicable data privacy laws you have the right to information as well as the right to rectification, blocking and deletion of your personal data. If deletion conflicts with any legal, contractual, commercial or fiscal record retention periods or with any other legally binding reasons, the data must be blocked instead of deleted.

### Your Consent

By using our website, you will be deemed to consent to our privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this website.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions or notification regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us at the email .
